[Music]
[Música]
let's see ivay criticizes in his live that they
a ver ivay critica en su directo que le
tell his friends on social media that they
digan en redes a sus amigos que se la
suck off man let's see there are some
chupan hombre a ver es que hay algunos
that are not your friends that's why they tell them
que no son tus amigos por eso le dicen
that they suck you off and in the afternoon with
que te la chupan and por la tarde con
our lifelong friends
nuestros amigos de toda la vida
we keep the friends and friendships of
mantenemos los amigos y las amistades de
10 12 years ago and and those people who are
hace 10 12 años y Y esa gente a la que
pissed off the truth is curious it is curious
le jode la verdad es curioso es curioso
there is one thing Clearly it refers to
hay una cosa Claro es que se refiere a
people who were already friends of him before
gente que ya era amigo de él antes de de
many years before he broke it a
hace muchos años antes de él petarlo
lot very curious what happens that catches my
mucho muy curiosa que pasa que me llama
attention too and the other day for
la atención también y el otro día por
example it happened to Cacho Cacho
ejemplo le pasó a Cacho Cacho el culo de
Cacho's ass the other day he got angry on Twitter
Cacho el otro día se enfadó en Twitter
because of this they consider that for
por esto ellos consideran que por
example all my friends okay well or or
ejemplo todos mis amigos vale bueno o o
there are people who consider that all my
hay gente que considera que todos mis
friends people that obviously don't like me I understand
amigos gente que evidentemente les caigo
are [ __ ] which
mal entiendo son unos chupapollas cosa
they are absolutely right not
que tienen toda la razón del mundo no
basically they consider that all my
básicamente consideran que todos mis
friends are [ __ ] okay And this
amigos son unos chupapollas vale Y esto
happened to Cacho the other day on Twitter I
le pasó a Cacho el otro día en Twitter
know with a follower because Cacho
lo sé con un seguidor porque Cacho lo
quoted him and  I was very angry no and I told him a lot
citó y estaba muy enfadado no y cacho le
Hey but one thing Dallas doesn't
decía Oye pero una cosa Dallas no se
get along with that little group remember
lleva bien con ese grupito recuerda
when he fought freely and whatever
cuando se peleó con libertad y lo que
comes up on a Minecraft server no
surja en un servidor de Minecraft no
but that didn't go any further that was an
pero eso no fue a más eso fue una
argument over a sanahoria Lisa
discusión por una sanahoria Lisa
Thank you so much for the gift queen
Muchísimas gracias por el regalo reina
But that didn't go any further eh that didn't go any
Pero eso no fue a más eh eso no fue a
further Hector a kiss that didn't go any further it didn't go any
más Héctor un beso eso no fue a más no
further let's say I don't remember
fue a más vamos digo yo no me acuerdo
but you'll see as much as
pero verás tú tanto como
this I don't know at what moment was the
este no sé en qué momento ha sido el
trigger for that rivalry the truth and
detonante para esa rivalidad la verdad y
Mario I've known him since before he was
Mario le conozco desde antes que fuera
famous dalis veira accentuated according to Javi
famoso dalis veira acentuado según Javi
and B Dalis veira spoke to him I put Here the
y B Le habló dalis veira puse Aquí el
Instagram yesterday or rather yesterday I opened here my
Instagram ayer o sea ayer abrí aquí mi
Instagram and I entered ibai's account and I
Instagram y entré en la cuenta de ibai y
opened the md I already in front of you guys I can't
abrí los md yo ya ante ustedes no puedo
do anything dal veira I can't really it's just
hacer nada dal veira no puedo de verdad
stupid to even force myself
es que es una tontería forzarse siquiera
and now he's become famous and he's still
y ahora se ha hecho famoso y y sigue
my friend I have to stop being
siendo mi amigo tengo que dejar de ser
his friend because if not I'm a [ __ ]
su amigo porque si no soy un chupapollas
It's weird sincerely I think there are people
Es raro sinceramente creo que hay gente
the one that bothers people having
a la que le molesta que la gente tenga
friends, the vast majority of my friends
amigos yo la gran mayoría de mis amigos
that I'm with on a
de los que estoy con ellos en el día a
daily basis know me since Javi. Not
día me conocen desde Javi por no estar
agreeing with Dallas on something doesn't
de acuerdo con Dalas en algo no
mean I'm his rival, man, if you
significa que sea su rival hombre si
add certain expressions and a certain tone,
añade ciertas expresiones y cierto tono
I do notice a certain tension in the environment,
Yo sí noto cierta tensión en el ambiente
eh. Forgive me. I don't agree with
eh Perdóname Yo no estoy de acuerdo con
Dallas on quite a few things, surely those
Dallas en bastantes cosas seguramente de
that we've discussed, but from there to
las que hemos tratado pero de ahí a
saying it with a certain tone, there's
a decirlo con cierta con cierto tono
cordiality or enmity, that's not what it's about,
está la cordialidad o la enemistad no es
not that I didn't have
la es de lo que trata no de que no tenía
money in the bank and now luckily I
dinero en el banco y ahora por suerte
have a lot more. But he's still my
tengo bastante más Pero sigue siendo mi
friend, I mean, what happens now is because I'm doing
amigo o sea qué pasa que ahora porque me
well professionally,
va bien profesionalmente
eh. No, I can't have friends. Or my friends
eh No no puedo tener amigos o mis amigos
that I had 12 years ago are
que tenía hace 12 años son unos
[ __ ], but they already sucked my dick 12
chupapollas pero ya me chupaba la [__]
years ago, but if 12 years ago I wasn't a
hace 12 años pero si hace 12 años no era
streamer, I don't understand it, I mean, in the end,
streamer no lo entiendo o sea al final
I suppose it's a, a mix of
Supongo que es una una una mezcla de de
envy, rage, and, I don't know, I don't
envidia de de rabia de de No lo sé no lo
understand it, I mean, a person who has known you for
entiendo o sea una persona que te conoce
12 years can still be
desde hace 12 años puede seguir siendo
your friend 12 years later  I mean, [ __ ],
tu amiga 12 años después es decir [__]
if Jud Bellingham has a
si jud bellingham tiene un amigo de la
childhood friend now because he's the [ __ ] boss of
infancia ahora porque es el [__] amo del
Real Madrid, he can't be his friend because he
Real Madrid no puede ser su amigo porque
's a [ __ ], it just doesn't make any
es un chupapollas es que no tiene ningún
sense. Another thing is that
tipo de sentido otra cosa es que se te
people approach you out of interest that they just
acerque gente por interés que te acaba
met recently, but if you know
de conocer hace poco pero si tú conoces
what I told you at the beginning, I mean, he's
lo que os he dicho al principio o sea se
referring to new people, people
está refiriendo a gente nueva a gente
who approach him because they are already because he
que se acerca a él porque son ya porque
is
es
and they are dedicated to this, not people that
y ellos se dedican a esto no gente que
you knew before, I don't know what, someone from
conozcas antes no sé qué alguien de la
childhood, [ __ ]. Now he has to stop
infancia [__] Ahora tiene que dejar de
being my friend because I'm known. It's weird,
ser mi amigo porque soy conocido Es raro
really, everyone
realmente todo el mundo que tengo
around me is only my friend because
alrededor solamente es mi amigo porque
he's a [ __ ] and absolutely
es un chupapollas y absolutamente a
nobody likes me, a lot of people
nadie le caigo bien bastante gente
for sure, I mean, this thing, dedicating yourself to
seguro o sea es que esto el dedicarte a
this and well, when things are going well for you and you
esto y bueno cuando te va bien no y
succeed, well, the [ __ ] you have is that,
triunfa pues la [__] que tienes es esa
man, it's disgusting, but that's how it is. Hey, I'm
tío es un asco pero es así Oye estoy
watching how the video is going, the
viendo cómo va el vídeo el canal
main channel, I'm done with it, okay.
principal le estoy hecho el bacillo vale
Well, the subject has eased up a bit, but the
Bueno ya aflojó un poco el tema pero la
truth is that it's not going, it's not going badly. What
verdad es que no va no está yendo mal Lo
has turned yellow for me is
que sí que se me ha puesto en Amarillo
again one guy they're leaving me they're
otra vez uno tío se me van se me van
putting in Yellow the videos of the
poniendo en Amarillo los vídeos de la
Jeffre series all One by one I mean
serie de jeffre todos Uno por uno o sea
first the first one was put
primero se puso el primero el primero se
in Yellow It was confirmed in Yellow a
puso en Amarillo Se confirmó en Amarillo
week later the second one was put in
a la semana el segundo se puso en
Yellow It was confirmed and now
Amarillo Se confirmó y ahora se me acaba
the third one has just been put in Yellow and
de poner en Amarillo el tercero que
now when you send it for review It will
ahora cuando lo mandas a revisión
probably be
Seguramente se
confirmed I'm such a shitty person that
confirme soy tan [__] de persona a que
nobody likes me in a natural
a nadie le caigo bien de manera natural
and organic way maybe we'll talk about
y orgánica puede que sí hablaremos de
this debate in the next live shows it's
este debate en próximos directos es
incredible I mean I want to think that
increíble O sea quiero pensar que a
someone likes me because yes you know Not
alguien le caigo bien porque sí sabes No
only because they have an interest in getting
solo porque tenga un interés en sacarme
something from me I don't know I want to think it no but that
algo yo que sé quiero pensarlo no pero
has nothing to do with it I mean you
no tiene nada que ver eso o sea tú
can like them even if they're
puedes caerle bien incluso aunque se
approaching you for interest another
esté acercando por ti por interés otra
thing is that they wouldn't have been interested in getting to
cosa es que no se hubiera interesado en
know you to know if they like you or
conocerte para saber si le caes bien o
not if you weren't who you are and if they
mal si no fueras quién eres y si
only like me for some kind
solamente les caigo bien por algún tipo
of interest then I'll go to bed and
de interés pues me iré a la cama y
cry while eating ice cream hack and
Lloraré mientras como un helado hack and
DS the curse of jeffre estein
DS la maldición de jeffre estein me
want to silence me the elite
quieren silenciar los de la élite me
want me  silence saying this guy What's
quieren silenciar diciendo este tío Qué
up he charges money for videos boom that he does
pasa cobra pasta por los vídeos pum que
n't charge like that he gets lazy and now
no cobre así le da pereza y ya nce más
your camera looks bad Javi I've noticed
se ve mal tu cámara Javi lo he notado
that it's dirty today I've noticed that it's
que hoy está como sucia lo he notado que
dirty today right I mean it looks like it's like I've
hoy está como sucia verdad O sea se ve
put my fingers in it right Let's
hubiera puesto los dedos verdad A
see it happens a lot because I touch it and move it
ver pasa mucho porque la toco y la muevo
Look it's just improved a little right
Mira justo ha mejorado un poco verdad
Javi got involved with Jorge Javier I don't deny it
Javi se Lio con Jorge Javier no lo niego
Gran Canaria I don't deny it at
gran canario no lo niego absolutamente
all but [ __ ] I don't know I want to
para nada pero [__] no sé quiero
think that there are things in life that are
pensar que hay cosas en la vida que son
so natural and simple like I've met
tan naturales y simples como he conocido
someone and I like them and that's it I mean I don't
a alguien y me cae bien y punto o sea no
feel like you promoting me or
me apetece que me hagas promoción ni que
buying me a house I just like you
me compres una casa simplemente me caes
on telesalseo it looked so-so
bien en telesalseo se veía regulín
too Yeah better not Better not that I can be seen looking
también Sí mejor no Mejor no que se me
pink no that I can be seen well
vea ver roso no que se me vea bien no
I'm not an eyesore sometimes
soy un disgusto para la vista a veces
carch is an IB npc who used to be an
carch es un npc de IB que antes era npc
auron npc Well there are people who have
de auron Bueno hay gente que
literally spent their entire career
literalmente su carrera
and
la ha la ha pasado y la
based it on that eh There are  people who have
ha la ha basado en eso eh Hay gente que
literally based their career on that have
su carrera literalmente la ha basado en
now become famous and what do I do?
eso ahora se ha hecho famoso y qué hago
Stop being their friend. I think it's
dejo de ser su colega Yo creo que es
people there who don't like it, no. I
gente ahí que que no le Mola no Yo
suppose that people who
supongo que no le Mola a la gente que
have friends don't like it and it makes them angry because
tiene amigos y le da rabia porque
probably that person wants to be
probablemente esa persona quiera ser
Cacho and wants to play with DJ Mario open
Cacho y quiera jugar con DJ Mario abrir
Fifa packs, man has subscribed
sobres de Fifa hombre se ha suscrito
virus virus 4 months subscribed [ __ ] vir
virus virus 4 meses suscritos [__] vir
is motivated with the evening eh viruz
está motivado con la velada eh viruz
is motivated with the evening he is
está motivado con la velada está
putting Push virus is going to the evening
metiendo Push virus va a la velada
so virus can fight after
entonces virus puede pelear después de
last year's injury he says totally you
la lesión del año pasado dice totalmente
are difficult to watch Hahaha Well you see me
eres difícil de ver Jajaja Pues tú me
24 hours beautiful Javi
ves 24 horas guapa Javi a ti te quedó de
your hair operation was a 10 yes the truth is that
10 tu operación de pelo sí la verdad que
I am crazy happy with the
estoy loquísimo de contento con la
hair operation crazy happy
operación de pelo loquísimo de contento
I spend the whole [ __ ] day looking at my hair
Estoy todo el [__] día mirándome el pelo
but the worst thing is that well the worst
pero es que lo peor es que bueno lo peor
Not the best What are you saying this you get into okay okay we have
No lo mejor Qué dices esito te metes
the face of Dallas
vale vale tenemos la cara de Dallas
we have the face of Dallas boom well I don't
tenemos la cara de Dallas pum pues yo no
see it it will look bad I see it Flama let's
lo veo que quedará mal lo veo Flama
see the hair  I'm super happy with my
a ver el pelo estoy super contento con
hair man but the thing about my hair is
el pelo tío pero la movida del pelo es
that it's not the result yet. I didn't
que no es el resultado todavía yo no me
expect to look like this in January
esperaba que para enero me viera así
but I started to notice it well on the trip
pero empecé a notarlo bien en el viaje
to Asturias man, in the photographs
de Asturias tío en las fotografías
when you take photos, wow, what amazing hair I have
cuando me haas fotos [__] vaya pelazo
and I really didn't expect to
que se me ve y realmente no me esperaba
see it like this now eh I think it's been 4 months no let's
ver así ya eh 4 meses creo que llevo no
see it was October it was the first of
a ver fue octubre fue primero de
September I think it was the operation no
septiembre creo que fue la operación no
September October November December
septiembre octubre noviembre diciembre
already January is going to be almost 5 months
ya Enero ya va a ser casi 5 meses
eh in theory the result Well both the
eh en teoría el resultado Bueno tanto el
result of the pills Not that it
resultado de las pastillas No que te
gives you hair as more eh with more quality
pone el pelo como más eh con más calidad
and everything and that the hair grows because in the
y demás y que crezca el pelo porque al
end a month or so after the operation it falls out it falls
final al mes y pico de la operación se
out again the one that was
te cae se te vuelve a caer el que ha
put in I became bald again and it
puesto me volví a quedar calvo y y
starts growing zero And the truth is that it looks
empieza a crecer cero Y es que se ve
super good after the summer
super bien la verdad después del verano
Well I think that in the summer it's going to
Bueno yo creo que en verano ya se va a
look impressive eh of course the treatment is
ver impresionante eh claro tramiento es
for life Ruben the treatment if you
de por vida Rubén el tratamiento si te
stop taking it the fall out continues its
lo dejas de tomar la caída sigue su
course The new one stays and the fall out
curso Se te queda el nuevo y la caída
behind continues its course you know but
por detrás sigue su curso sabes pero
But it turned out very well  It's true that I
Pero ha quedado muy bien la verdad que
'm very happy I would have done it
estoy muy contento me lo hubiera hecho
before if Well yes it's true that
antes si Bueno sí que verdad es que
before I didn't have the same tickets man
antes no tenía las mismas entradas tío
I see myself in videos from 2019 and 2020 and such
yo me veo en vídeo del 2019 y 2020 y tal
And I don't have the tickets that I had this
Y no tengo las entradas que tenía este
year Mine was a thing of two years I don't know
año lo mío fue cosa de de dos años no sé
if it was stress from being busier I don't know
si fue estrés por estar más liado no sé
the truth the move I have no [ __ ]
la verdad la mudanza no tengo ni [__]
idea the truth but it was in the last
idea la verdad pero fue en los últimos
in the last two years when I have already
en el últimos dos años cuando ya me he
said to myself Ugh I need to get involved to be
dicho yo Uf a hace falta mete mano para
in the evening eh byus eh what do you
estar en la velada eh byus eh qué
think Javi let's see here the
pensáis Javi veremos aquí el vídeo de
Dallas video is already public now we see a
Dallas ya está público ahora vemos un
piece of viirus in the evening people
trozo de viirus en la velada gente
sincere opinion let's talk
opinión sincera vamos a hablar
sincerely about this I mean what do you
sinceramente sobre esto O sea qué
think Honestly about this eh
opináis Honestamente sobre esto eh De
Really and go What the [ __ ] is he
verdad y va Le qué [__] le que está
uploading boxing stories all day long [ __ ] let's
subiendo todo el día histories de boxeo
see there's not much vairus so
[__] a ver no hay mucho vairus entonces
yes he participates in the evening despite the
sí participa en la velada a pesar de la
injury he had such a delicate mystery the
lesión que tuvo tan delicad misterio el
other day virus to Instagram three or
otro día virus a Instagram hace tres o
four days ago you sent it to me in the chat he
cuat días me lo pasasteis por el chat le
said hi we fight no  there are balls or so
dijo jelao peleamos no hay huevos o sea
he really is let's see let's see he
él verdad que está a ver vamos a ver él
's at full blast I mean the hint is
está a tope O sea la indirecta es
quite clear I mean the hint is
bastante Clara O sea la indirecta es
I'm naked in my house Come on but but let's
Estoy desnudo en mi casa Ven pero pero a
see the other day I uploaded a story that it
ver el otro día sub una history que que
was quite obvious what was
era bastante evidente lo que estaba
happening no Let's see let's read opinions
pasando no A ver vamos a leer opiniones
the virus will be vaccinated no the virus already
el virus estará vacunado no el virus ya
came up a thing already came up
subió una movida subió ya el test
this anti-doping test and now and now it came out
antidoping este y ya y ya le salió
negative it came out negative I mean
negativo ya le salió negativo o sea
absolutely clean absolutely
absolutamente limpio absolutamente
clean
limpio
[Music]
[Música]
ta
ta